Mass Production Part Assurance Report					Product Name : Television				
									
									
Part Name     : Adaptor				Part Number     : EAY63129801			Month          : Aug'2017		
Lot/ASN No. : AP417050007307			Supplier Name : Asian Power						
Judgement   : OK						Event   : MP Assurance			
									
Test Details									
Sr No	Name	Method	Judgement	Samples	Start Date	End Date	Tests Image	Result	Remark
1	High Temp Load Test	"Keep sample at 60â„ƒ (High temp. chamber), Apply Voltage rating to it with Max load for 96 Hr"	"Expose it at the room temp. for more than 2hr, then check standard outKeep voltage after test"	2	3-Aug-17	7-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
2	Low Temp.Load Test	"Keep a sample at 0â„ƒ (Low temp. chamber), Apply Voltage rating to it with Max load for 96 Hrs"	"Expose it at the room temp. for more than 2hr, then check standard outKeep voltage after test"	2	4-Aug-17	8-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
3	On/Off Test	Apply maximum load to the adaptor at 40â„ƒ high temp. chamber. Carry out 4sec. On / 1sec off for 168 hrs under the condition of voltage rating AC 220V / 50Hz	Check standard outKeep voltage after test	2	5-Aug-17	12-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
4	Withstanding Voltage Test	Apply AC 3 KV voltage for 1 min	It should pass HV test	2	12-Aug-17	12-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
5	Insulation Resistance	When applying DC 500V between terminals and sheath for one minute.	It should pass IR test	2	12-Aug-17	12-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
6	Dropping Test	"Drop each 6 sides each time. For Portable Adaptor (1M), power supply (0.7M) height on top on griddle block/Steel Plate"	"After testing there should be No Exterior / interior damage, deformation of structure"	2	12-Aug-17	12-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
7	Breakdown structure Test	After Open Case check soldering state of the connection site of the Cord of internal and Solder Ball confirmation.	ther should Not any abnormality	1	12-Aug-17	12-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
8	Plug-breaking strength Test (Integrated Adaptor On	Press weight of 40kg at Plug by UTM Equipment.	There shall be no damage and deformation	2	12-Aug-17	12-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
9	Plug-breaking strength Test (Integrated Adaptor On	Press weight of 40kg at Plug by UTM Equipment.	There shall be no damage and deformation	2	12-Aug-17	12-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
10	Alcohol Resistance Test	Rub the printing surface with force of 1 Kgf using ethyl alcohol test jig for 10 times	No erase of print	2	12-Aug-17	12-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
11	Moisture load test	"Put the adaptor 40â„ƒ, 95% constant humidity chamber, voltage rating (MAX Load), 12 hours ON / 12 Time OFF to conduct 96 hours."	"Expose it at the room temp. for more than 2hr, then check standard output voltage after test"	2	12-Aug-17	16-Aug-17	No Img	OK	
Comment									
									
									
									
			Checked By		Verified By		Approved By		
									
									
LG (ILP) QAS 009 (02042015)-00								LGE PUNE	
